RYAN SYME

Web Developer

SUMMARY

During my career, I have developed several skills in working with both computers and numbers I have the ability to properly manage, organize and analyze information and present that information in a clear and concise manner. I have worked in many different positions, including managerial positions and have experience in working alone, within a group and as a leader.

CONTACT INFO:

SKILLS:

Dalbyvägen 50a
761 54,
Norrtälje
ryansyme@outlook.com
(+46) 70 037 6163

FRONT END:	BACK END:	ASSETS:
HTML	PYTHON	XD
CSS	DJANGO	GITHUB
JAVASCRIPT	FLASK	GITPOD
REACT	MONGODB	BALSAMIQ
BOOTSTRAP	SQL / NOSQL	GIMP
JQUERY		

EMPLOYMENT

Full-Stack Web Developer

FREELANCE

JAN 2021 - ONGOING

- Web Design
- Front-End Development
- Back-End Development
- Available for both individual and group collaborations

CAD Designer

SYMECAD

JUN 2018 - DEC 2020

Freelance computer-assisted design of rooms, for construction and remodeling companies to show virtual presentation booklets of their remodels to customers

Responsible for all aspects of a CAD Design Company including:

- CAD Design
- Customer Service
- Time Management
- Accounting

Business Owner

NORDIC GLOW LTD

MAY 2014 - AUG 2015

Owner and Creator of a E-Cigarette company.

Responsible for all aspects of an Internet E-Commerce business including:

- Product Design
- Customer Service
- Budgeting and Accounting
- Purchasing and Sales

EDUCATION

Code Institute, Dublin

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

University Accredited course covering all aspects of web development including:

- UX
- Front-End
- Back-End
- Documentation

NTI Komvux, Norrtälje

JAN 2020 - MAY 2020

- Web Development 1
- Web Development 2

NTI Komvux, Norrtälje

AUG 2012 - MAR 2014

- Accounting 1
- Accounting 2
- Business Economy 1
- Business Economy 2
- Computer Science
- Computer and Network Technology

Palmers College, Grays, England

SEP 1996 - MAY 1998

- Statistics
- Physics
- Biology